Guide to the Lillian D. Wald Papers
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series I: Cataloged Correspondence
  - Lehman, Herbert Henry from the Henry Street Settlemen~ 1918-1919 (Box 7)
  - Lehman, Herbert Henry to LDW; 5 October 1918 (Box 7)
  - Lehman, Herbert Henry to Dorothy Cofnn; 31 March 1919 (Box 7)
  - Lehman, Herbert Henry to Viola P. Conklin; 16 April 1919 -25 June 1919 (Box 7)
  - Lehman, Herbert Henry to Marion S. Brown; 2 September 1919 (Box 7)
  - Lehman, Herbert Henry to LDW; S December 1919 (Box 7)
  - Lehman, Herbert Henry to Viola P. Conklin; 8 April 1920 -28 October 1920 (Box 7)
  - Lehman, Herbert Henry to LDW; 28 October 1931 (Box 7)
  - Lehman, Herbert Henry to Abraham N. Davis; 29 January 1929 (Box 7)
  - Lehman, Herbert Henry to LDW; 3 November 1921 (Box 7)
  - Lehman, Herbert Henry to Elsa H. Herrmann; 23 January 1924 (Box 7)
  - Lehman, Herbert Henry to Mabel Coleman; 26 January 1924 (Box 7)
  - Lehman, Herbert Henry to LDW; 24 December 1924 (Box 7)
  - Lehman. Herbert Henry to Felix M. Warburg; 13 January 1925 (Box 7)
  - Lehman, Herbert Henry to Mabel Coleman; 20 August 1925 (Box 7)
  - Lehman, Herbert Henry to LDW; 30 November 1926 -I December 1926 (Box 7)
  - Lehman, Herbert Henry to Mabel Coleman; 28 March 1928 (Box 7)
  - Lehman, Herbert Henry to Karl O. Hesley; 10 December 1928 (Box 7)
  - Lehman, Herbert Henry to Theodore O. Siege~ 5 February 1929 -6 February [I929] (Box 7)
  - Lehman, Herbert Henry to Karl O. Hesley; 27 January 1931 (Box 7)
  - Lehman, Herbert Henry to LDW; 10 March [1933J (Box 7)
  - Lehman, Sissie Straus (Mrs. Irving) to LDW; n.d. (Box 7)
  - Lindsay, Samuel McCune to LDW; 3 July 1909 -10 March 1933 (Box 7)
  - Lippmann, Fay Albertson (Mn. Walter) to LDW; 18 November [1926J (Box 7)
  - Loeb, Jacques to LDW; 2 June 1912 -11 January 1917 (Box 7)
  - Long, Breckinridge to Henry Morgenthau; 30 December [I919J (Box 7)
  - Longworth, Nicholas to LDW; I July 1926 (Box 7)
  - Low, Seth to LDW; 25 March 1901 -21 December 1915 (Box 7)
  - McCleUan, Goorge Brinton to LDW; 20 February 1905 (Box 7)
  - McCIeUan, George Brinton to Jacob Henry Schiff; 25 January 1909 (Box 7)
  - McConooll, Francis John to LDW; 17 March 1930 (Box 7)
  - McCormack, Cyrus Hall to LDW; 2 February 1926 (Box 7)
  - MacDonald, James Ramsay to LDW; 19 June 1905 -21 September 1909 (Box 7)
  - McDowell, Henry Burden to LDW; 2 January 1908 (Box 7)
  - MacKaye, Percy to LDW; 12 August 1908 (Box 7)
  - McMurtrie, Douglas C. to LDW; 18 November 1918 (Box 7)
  - Macy, Edith W. Carpenter(Mn. V. Everit) to LDW; n.d. -30 November 1917 (Box 7)
  - Macy, V. Everitt to LDW; 13 December 19O5 -[1910J (Box 7)
  - Macy, V. Everitt to Viola P. Conklin; 31 January 1910 (Box 7)
  - Macy, V. Everitt to LDW; 23 July 1910 -3 October 191 (Box 7)
  - Macy. V. Everitt to Viola P. Conklin; 4 December 1911 (Box 7)
  - Macy. V. Everitt; from the Henry Street Settlement; 1912-1922 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Macy. V. Everitt to LDW; 7 January 1914 -26 August 1919 (Box 7, Folder 13 to 21)
  - Macy, V. Everitt to Dorothy Coffin; 10 October 1919 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Macy, V. Everitt to LDW; & March 1920 21 November 1929 (Box 7, Folder 23 to 33)
  - Macy. V. Everitt. Jr. to LDW; 8 November 1926 -31 December 1926 (Box 7, Folder 1 to 2)
  - Marbury, Elizabeth to LDW; Slune 1923 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Martin, Edward Sandford to LDW; n.d. -23 March 1904 (Box 7, Folder 1 to 4)
  - Masaryk, Thomas Garrigue to LDW; 31 October 1918 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Maude, Aylmer to LDW; 16 April 1926 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Mead. Lucia True Ames (Mrs. Edwin D.) to LDW; 4 February 1917 -16 September 1919 (Box 7, Folder 1 to 3)
  - Meeker. Royal to LDW; 13 September 1916 -28 November 1919 (Box 7, Folder 1 to 2)
  - Meiklejohn, Alexander to Crystal Eastotan; 7 February 1916 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Mitchel, John Purroy to LDW; 4 November 1910 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Montefiore, Claude loseph G. to 7; 22 February 1911 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Moore,lohn Bassett to LDW; 161anuary 1915 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Morgan, Anne to LDW; 6 May 1914 13 September 1915 (Box 7, Folder 1 to 3)
  - Morgenthau. Elinor Fatman (Mes. Henry, Jr.) to LDW; [1925) (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Morgenthau, Henry to LDW; 30 October n.y. -10 March 1933 (Box 7, Folder 1 to 12)
  - Morgenthau, Henry, Jr. to LDW; 9 March 1933 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Morgenthau. Josephine Sykes (Mrs. Henry) to LDW: 12 August n.y. -[October 1926] (Box 7, Folder 1 to 4)
  - Moses. Robert to Viola Percy Conklin; 30 December 1919 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Munro. David Alexander to LDW; 2S November 1904 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Murray, Arthur to LDW; 1 December 1928 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Nagel, Charles to LDW; 7 August 1909-11 October 1912 (Box 8, Folder 1 to 3)
  - Nearing, Scott to LDW; 20 February [1916] (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Ochs, Adolph S. to 1929 -24 December 1929 (Box 8, Folder 1 to 2)
  - Ochs, Effie Miriam Wise (Mrs. Adolph S.) to LDW; 2 March 1926 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Odell. BenjanUn B .• Jr. to Isaac N. Seligman; 14 March 1904 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Ovington, Mery White to LDW; 31une 1915 -26 December 1917 (Box 8, Folder 1 to 2)
  - Ovington. Mary White to 1; 16 October -3 December 1919 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Ovington, Mary White to LDW; 61anuary 1920 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Pankhurst, Emmeline Goulden to LDW; 13 October 1911 -19 October 1911 (Box 8, Folder 1 to 2)
  - Parsons, Herbert to LDW; 24 February 1914 -2& May 1922 (Box 8, Folder 1 to 3)
  - Peabody, George Livingston to LDW; 4 May 1911 (Box 8, Folder 1 to 2)
  - Perkins, Frances to LDW; 9 February 191& -17 lune 1918 (Box 8, Folder 1 to 3)
  - Perkins, Frances to Rebecca Schatz; 19 November 1918 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Perkins, Frances to LDW; 22 March 1919 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Perkins, Frances to Viola P. Conklin; 10 April 1919 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Perkins, Frances to LDW; 25 June 1921 -[1931] (Box 8, Folder 7 to 14)
  - Perkins. Frances to Karl D. Hesley; 18 February 1931 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Perkins, Frances to LDW; 13 June 1931 -10 March 1933 (Box 8, Folder 16 to 17)
  - Pethick-Lawrence, Emmeline Pethick. Lady Pethick-Lawrence to LDW; 19 November (1914)-18 January 1926 (Box 8, Folder 1 to 7)
    On Reel 7 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Pethick-Lawrence, Frederick William to LDW; 18 January 1926 -18 January 1926 (Box 8, Folder 1 to 2)
  - Pinehott Amos to LDW; 11 January 1917 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Pinchot, Gifford to LDW; 9 December n.y. -28 February 1929 (Box 8, Folder 1 to 2)
  - Pine, John Barclay to LDW; 28 March 1917 -4 April 1917 (Box 8, Folder 1 to 2)
  - Pink, Louis Heaton to LDW; 20 May n.y. -2 December 1931 (Box 8, Folder 1 to 5)
  - Plimpton, George Arthur to LDW; 29 March n.y. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Pope, Arthur Upham to LDW; (1919)-5 December 1919 (Box 8, Folder 1 to 2)
  - Potter, Henry Cadman to LDW; 10 July n.y. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Potter, Henry Cadman to 1; 2 January 190] (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Potter, Henry Codman to LDW; 26 March 1901 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Price, Joseph M. to LDW; 6 January 1908 -26 July 1918 (Box 8, Folder 1 to 7)
  - Price. Joseph M. to the Friends of Russian Freedom; 8 August 1918 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Price, Joseph M. to LDW; 20 January 1919 -9 March 1933 (Box 8, Folder 9 to 12)
  - Pritchett, Henry Smith to LDW; 6 August 1902 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Pritchett. Henry Smith to Frances Colbourne; 4 April 1918 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Pritchett, Henry Smith to LDW; 3 February 1919 -17 September 1920 (Box 8, Folder 3 to 5)
  - Proskauer. Joseph M. to LDW; 26 April 1926 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Purdy, Lawson to LDW; 19 April 1923 -9 April 1928 (Box 8, Folder 1 to 5)
  - Rolph, Julian to LDW; IS July 1902 -21 December 1902 (Box 8, Folder 1 to 2)
  - Rankin. Jeannette to LDW; IS September 1917 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Reid, Helen Miles Rogers (Mrs. Ogden M.) to LDW; 10 April 1931 -27 April 1931 (Box 8, Folder 1 to 2)
  - Reynolds. James Bronson to LDW; 1 December 1904 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Reynolds, James Bronson to Florence Kelley; 30 January 1907 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Reynolds, James Bronson to LDW; IS July 1907 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Reynolds, James Bronson to 1; 12 October 1907 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Reynolds, James Bronson to LDW; 7 November 1907 -26 October 1914 (Box 8, Folder 5 to 7)
  - Reynolds. James Bronson to ... Friends of Russian Freedom.; 12 July 1918 -29 July 1918 (Box 8, Folder 8 to 9)
  - Reynolds, James Bronson to LDW; IS July 1919 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Rice, Elmer to LDW; 18 June 1931 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Richardson, Dorothy to LDW; 28 November 1905 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Riis, Elizabeth Nielsen (Mrs. Jacob A.) to LDW; 6 June 1900 -I October 1901 (Box 8, Folder 1 to 5)
  - Riis, Jacob August to LDW; 9 February n.y. -21 September 1911 (Box 8, Folder 1 to 27)
  - Riis, Mary Phillips (Mrs. Jacob A.) to LDW; [April 1933) (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Robinson, Frederick Bertrand to Karl D. Hesler. 12 November 1933 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, Abby Aldrich (Mrs. John D., Jr.) to LDW; 27 November n.y. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Rockefeller, John D., Jr. to LDW; 9 July n.y. -28 December 1912 (Box 8, Folder 1 to 2)
  - Rockefeller, John D .. Jr. to L. Emmett Hol~ 19 February 1917 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Rockefeller, John D., 3rd to LDW; 29 December 1930 -5 January 1931 (Box 8, Folder 1 to 2)
  - Roosevelt, Eleanor (Mrs. Franklin D.) to LDW; 4 January 1927 -(1933) (Box 8, Folder 1 to 2)
  - Rothschild, Carola Warburg (Mrs. Walter) to LDW; n.d. -10 March 1933 (Box 8, Folder 1 to 2)
  - Rothschild, Walter to LDW; 3 July 1922 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Roussy de Sales; Lily (Counte .. Jean de) to LDW; 12 January 1931 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Rowe, Leo S. to LDW; 10 March 1933 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Samuel. Edwin Herbert, 2nd Viscount Samuel to LDW; 14 September (1931) 17 October (1931) (Box 9, Folder 1 to 4)
  - Sanger, Margaret Higgins to LDW; 20 April 1921 -9 March 1929 (Box 9, Folder 1 to 7)
  - Sanger, Margaret Higgins to Karl O. Hesley; 28 March 1931 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Sanger, Margaret Higgins to LDW; I October 1931 -20 October 1931 (Box 9, Folder 9 to 10)
  - Scbeu-Riesz. Helene to LDW; 7 December 1925 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Schieffelin, William Jay to LDW; 6 February 1919 -3 November 1926 (Box 9, Folder 1 to 3)
  - Schiff, Adele O. Neustadt (Mrs. Mortimer L.) to LDW; 14 January n.y. [1925] (Box 9, Folder 1 to 4)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to LDW; January 1901 -24 September 1908 (Box 9, Folder 1 to 54)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to LDW; (1909)-20 January 1909 (Box 9, Folder 55 to 58)
    On Reel 8 of the Wald Microfilm
  - SchifJacob Henry to Thatcher M. Brown; IS February 1909 -19 February 1909 (Box 9, Folder 59 to 60)
  - SchifJacob Henry to LDW; 23 February 1909 -13 January 1910 (Box 9, Folder 61 to 76)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to Thatcher M. Brown; 20 January 1910 (Box 9, Folder 77)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to LDW; 26 January 1910 -27 November 1910 (Box 9, Folder 78 to 88)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to Mabel T. Boardman; 30 November 1910 (Box 9, Folder 89)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to LDW; 20 December 1910 -3 January 1911 (Box 9, Folder 90 to 92)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to Thatcher M. Brown; 9 January 1911 (Box 9, Folder 93)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to LDW; February 1911 -7 December 1911 (Box 9, Folder 94 to 98)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to Viola P. Conklin; 19 December 1911 (Box 9, Folder 99)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to LDW; 29 December 1911 -30 August 1912 (Box 9, Folder 100 to 105)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to Viola P. Conklin; 20 September 1912 (Box 9, Folder 106)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to LDW; 26 September 1912 -April 1914 (Box 9, Folder 107 to 109)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to Viola P. Conklin; 4 May 1914 (Box 9, Folder 110)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to LDW; 18 May -December 1914 (Box 9, Folder 111)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to LDW; 1 March 1915 -10 March 1915 (Box 10, Folder 112 to 113)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to Lavinia L. Dock; 20 May 1915 (Box 10, Folder 114)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to LDW; 20 May 1915 -2 July 1915 (Box 10, Folder 115 to 117)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to Viola P. Conklin; 9 July 1915 (Box 10, Folder 118)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to LDW; October 1915 -4 April 1918 (Box 10, Folder 119 to 128)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to Viola P. Conklin; 19 April 1918 (Box 10, Folder 129)
  - Schiff,Jacob Henry to LDW; 22 April 1918 -24 April 1918 (Box 10, Folder 130 to 131)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to Viola P. Conklin; 2 May 1918 -7 May 1918 (Box 10, Folder 132 to 133)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to LDW; 16 May 1918 (Box 10, Folder 134)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to Viola P. Conklin; 14 June 1918 (Box 10, Folder 135)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to LDW; 25 June 1918 -2 July 1918 (Box 10, Folder 136 to 137)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to Dorothy Coffin; 16 July 1918 (Box 10, Folder 138)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to LDW; 9 August 1918 (Box 10, Folder 139)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to Dorothy Caffin; 2 September 1918 -1 November 1918 (Box 10, Folder 140 to 144)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to LDW; 6 November 1918 -7 November 1918 (Box 10, Folder 145 to 146)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to Viola Percy Conklin; 27 November 1918 (Box 10, Folder 147)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to Dorothy Carfin; 3 December 1918 -5 December 1918 (Box 10, Folder 148 to 149)
  - SchifJacob Henry to Viola P. Conklin; 26 December 1918 (Box 10, Folder 150)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to LDW; 27 December 1918 (Box 10, Folder 151)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to Viola P. Conklin; 13 January 1919 (Box 10, Folder 152)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to LDW; 16 January 1919 (Box 10, Folder 153)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to Dorothy Caffin; 17 January 1919 -20 January 1919 (Box 10, Folder 154 to 155)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to Helen G. Strong; 24 January 1919 (Box 10, Folder 156)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to Dorothy Caffin; 28 January 1919 (Box 10, Folder 157)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to LDW; 2 February 1919 (Box 10, Folder 158)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to Dorothy Carfin; 10 February 1919 -17 February 1919 (Box 10, Folder 159 to 160)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to LDW; 25 February 1919 -3 March 1919 (Box 10, Folder 161 to 165)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to Dorothy Camn; 10 March 1919 (Box 10, Folder 166)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to Viola P. Conklin; 19 March 1919 (Box 10, Folder 167)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to LDW; 25 March 1919 (Box 10, Folder 168)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to Dorothy Carfin; 4 April 1919 (Box 10, Folder 169)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to Viola P. Conklin; 16 April 1919 (Box 10, Folder 170)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to Dorothy Coffin; 21 May 1919 -6 June 1919 (Box 10, Folder 171 to 172)
    On Reel 9 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to LDW; 11 June 1919 -12 August 1919 (Box 10, Folder 173 to 175)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to Viola P. Conklin; 18 August 1919 -25 August 1919 (Box 10, Folder 176 to 177)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to LDW; 25 August 1919 -18 March 1920 (Box 10, Folder 178 to 192)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to Viola P. Conklin; 31 March 1920 (Box 10, Folder 193)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to LDW; 1 April 1920 -25 April 1920 (Box 10, Folder 194 to 195)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to V. Everit Macy; 4 May 1920 (Box 10, Folder 196)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to Viola P. Conklin; 7 June 1920 (Box 10, Folder 197)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry to LDW; 20 July 1920 (Box 10, Folder 198)
  - Schiff, Jacob Henry. from the Henry Street Settlement; 1908-1920 (Box 10, Folder 199)
  - Schiff, John M. to LDW; 7 March 1932 -10 March 1932 (Box 10, Folder 1 to 2)
  - Schiff, John M. to Karl O. Hesley; 18 May 1832 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Schiff, John M. to LDW; 10 March 1933. (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Schiff, Mortimer L. to Thatcher M. Brown; [November 1903] (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Schiff, Mortimer L. to F.R. Cordley; 1 J December 1903 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Schiff, Mortimer L. to LDW; II January 1904 -6 July 1911 (Box 10, Folder 3 to 11)
  - Schiff, Mortimer L. to Viola P. Conklin; 20 July 1916 -3 May 1918 (Box 10, Folder 12 to 13)
  - Schiff, Mortimer L. to LDW; 5 June 1918 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Schiff, Mortimer L. to (Viola P. Conklint 6 June 1918 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Schiff, Mortimer L. to LDW; 12 June 1918 -8 October 1920 (Box 10, Folder 16 to 20)
  - Schiff, Theresa Loeb (Mrs. JaeobH.) to LDW; 1 January.n.y.-17 March 1919 (Box 11, Folder 1 to 5)
  - Schiff, Theresa Loeb (Mrs. Jacob H.) to Viola P. Conklin; 10 June (1919) (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Schiff, Theresa Loeb (Mrs. Jacob H.) to LDW; 6 December 1920 -(January 1932) (Box 11, Folder 7 to 10)
  - Sedgwick, Ellery to LDW; 7 October 1914 -10 March 1933 (Box 11, Folder 1 to 24)
  - Seligman, Caroline Beer (Mrs. Edwin R.A.) to LDW; 7 March (1931) (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Seligman, Edwin Robert Anderson to LDW; 1 May 1901 -16 November 1910 (Box 11, Folder 1 to 2)
  - Seligman, GUIa Loeb (Mrs. Isaac N.) to (LDW); n.d. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Seligman. Isaac Newton to LDW; I July 1901 -21 December 1906 (Box 11, Folder 1 to 3)
  - Shaw, Albert to LDW; 30 November 1904 -28 October 1931 (Box 11, Folder 1 to 2)
  - Shotwell, James T. and others to LDW; 26 February 1930 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Slosson, Edwin Emery to LDW; (December 1919) -29 March 1920 (Box 11, Folder 1 to 3)
  - Smith, Alfred E. and others to LDW; 10 March 1933 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Smith. Mary R. to LDW; 2S-27 April o.y. and n.d. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Smith, Mary R. to Ann Geddes; 7-8 May 1925 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Smith, Mary R. to LDW; 1931 8 n.d. (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Snowden, Ethel Annakin. Viscountess Snowden to LDW; 28 "November 19, 1918 May, 1931 (Box 11, Folder 1 to 2)
  - Sokoloff, Boris to LDW; 10 March (1933) (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Somerset, (Lndy) Isabella Caroline to LDW; 5 November n.y. (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Soule, George to Karl O. Hesley; 7 April 1932 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Spargo, John to LDW; 25 August 1908 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Stelzle, Charles to Margaret Brown; 6 February 1915 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Stelzle, Charles to LDW; January 1919 -22 July 1921 (Box 11, Folder 2 to 4)
  - Stelzle, Charles to Elizabeth A. Cullen; 10 August 1921 -19 August 1921 (Box 11, Folder 5 to 9)
  - Stelzle, Charles to Leo Arnstein; 25 August 1921 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Stelzle, Charles to E. A. Cullen; 9 September 1921 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Stelzle, Charles to LDW; 10 October 1921 -29 February 1924 (Box 11, Folder 12 to 16)
  - Stelzle, Charles to Elsa H. Herrmann; 4 April 1924 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Stelzle, Charles to William J. Tully; 10 April 1924 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Stelzle, Charles to LDW; (10 April 1924) (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Stelzle, Charles to Elsa H. Herrmann; 21 April 1924 -26 June 1924 (Box 11, Folder 20 to 23)
  - Stelzle, Charles to LDW; 23 March 1926 -6 April 1927 (Box 11, Folder 24 to 27)
  - Stokes, J.G. Phelps to LDW; 29 December 1903 -26 September 1916 (Box 11, Folder 1 to 7)
  - Stokes, J.G. Phelps to Viola P. Conklin; 21 March 1917 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Stokes, J.G. Phelps to LDW; 21 April 1917 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Stokes, Rose Harriet Pastor (Mrs. J.G. Phelps) to LDW; 6 January 1907 2 March 1931 (Box 11, Folder 1 to 8)
  - Stokowski, 018a Samaroff (Mn. Leopold) to LDW; 21 February 1931 25 April 1931 (Box 11, Folder 1 to 2)
  - Stone, Nahum Isaac to LDW; 17 May 1917 -13 December 1927 (Box 11, Folder 1 to 7)
  - Stover, Charles B. to LDW; 13 May 1901 -31 March 1915 (Box 11, Folder 1 to 14)
  - Straus, Jesse Isidor to LDW; 16 October 1931 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Straus, Nathau Jr. to LDW; 24 January 1929 -31 March 1931 (Box 11, Folder 1 to 4)
  - Sulzberger, Arthur Hays to LDW; 27 December 1926 -9 March 1933 (Box 11, Folder 1 to 5)
  - Sulzberger, Cyrus L. to LDW; 24 November 1916 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Sutherland, (Sir) William to [LDW]; 13 January 1916 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Swope, Herbert Bayard to LDW; 4 August 1928 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Swope, Mary Dayton Hill (Mn. Gerard) to LDW; 14 December 1924 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Tarbell, Ida M. to LDW; n.d. -21 January (1911) (Box 12, Folder 1 to 11)
    On Reel 10 of the Wald Microfilm
  - Tarbell, Ida M. to 7; (1918) (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Thomas. Norman to Committee on the Army Bill; 1 May 1917 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Thomas, Norman to LDW; 7 June 1917 -28 November 1931 (Box 12, Folder 2 to 17)
  - Thompson, Dorothy to LDW; 6 January 1919 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Tolstoy. Alexandre to LDW; 18 November 1931 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Vance, Arthur T. to LDW; 23 September 1929 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Vanderlip, Frank Arthur to LDW; 28 June 1902 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Veiller, Lawrence to LDW; 23 February 1904 -15 August 1906 (Box 12, Folder 1 to 7)
  - Veiller, Lawrence to the Push-Cart Commission; 13 September 1906 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Veiller. Lawrence to LDW; 29 October 1906 -17 July 1930 (Box 12, Folder 9 to 18)
  - Villard, Helen Frances Garrison to LDW; 15 January 1906 -1 June 1909 (Box 12, Folder 1 to 2)
  - Villard, Oswald Garrison to LDW; II July 1913 -10 March 1933 (Box 12, Folder 1 to 13)
  - Wagner, Robert to LDW; 5 January (1929) (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Wagner, Robert to Anna Hellyer; 9 January 1929 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Wagner, Robert to Karl O. Hesley; 8 March 1933 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Wagner, Robert to LDW; 10 March 1933 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Wagner, Robert to Karl D. Hesley; 12 April 1933 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Wallas, Ada Redford (Mn. Graham) to LDW; 10 June 1905 -10 October 1915 (Box 12, Folder 1 to 7)
  - Wallas, Graham to LDW; 6 July 1910 -16 August 1931 (Box 12, Folder 1 to 4)
  - Walter, Wilfrid to LDW; 24 November 1931 -I December 1931 (Box 12, Folder 1 to 2)
  - Warburs, Betsy to LDW; 9 March 1933 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Warburg, Erich M. to LDW; 13 September 1926 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Warburg, Felix M. to LDW; 30 January 1901 -17 December 1915 (Box 12, Folder 1 to 4)
  - Warburg, Felix M. to Viola P. Conklin; 17 January 1916 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Warburg, Felx M. to LDW; 19 January 1916 -21 January 1916 (Box 12, Folder 16 to 17)
  - Warburg, Felix M. to Viola P. Conklin; 17 February 1916 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Warburg. Felix M. to LDW; 23 February 1916 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Warburg, Felix M. to Viola P. Conklin; 28 February 1916 -2S October 1916 (Box 12, Folder 20 to 24)
  - Warburg. Felix M. to LDW; 22 November 1916 -27 December 1916 (Box 12, Folder 25 to 26)
  - Warburg, Felix M. to Viola P. Conklin; 25 January 1917 -24 December 1917 (Box 12, Folder 27 to 29)
  - Warburg, Felix M. to Dorothy CafCin; 31 December 1918 -3 May 1919 (Box 12, Folder 30 to 31)
  - Warburg, Felix M. to Viola P. Conklin; 3 June 1919 -9 September 1919 (Box 12, Folder 32 to 34)
  - Warburg, Felix M. to LDW; 9 January 1920 -15 May 1920 (Box 12, Folder 35 to 36)
  - Warburg, Felix M. to Viola P. Conklin; 22 October 1920 -4 April 1921 (Box 12, Folder 37 to 38)
  - Warburg, Felix M. to Mabel Coleman; 4 July 1921 -25 October 1921 (Box 12, Folder 39 to 44)
  - Warburg, Felix M. to LDW; 28 October 1921 (Box 12, Folder 45)
  - Warburg, Felix M. to Elsa H. Herrmann; 9 March 1922 (Box 12, Folder 46)
  - Warburg, Felix M. to Mabel Coleman; IS March 1922 (Box 12, Folder 47)
  - Warburg, Felix M. to Elsa H. Herrmann; 1S March 1922 (Box 12, Folder 48)
  - Warburg, Felix M. to LDW; 4 April 1922 (Box 12, Folder 49)
  - Warburg, Felix M. to Elsa H. Herrmann; 10 November 1922 -20 November 1922 (Box 12, Folder 50 to 51)
  - Warburg, Felix M. to Henry Street Settlement; 20 March 1923 (Box 12, Folder 52)
  - Warburg, Felix M. to Mabel Coleman; 12 July 1923 (Box 12, Folder 53)
  - Warburg, Felix M. to Elsa H. Herrmann; 14 December 1923 -9 October 1924 (Box 12, Folder 54 to 57)
  - Warburg, Felix M. to Anna E. Geddes; 14 January 1925 (Box 12, Folder 58)
  - Warburg, Felix M. to LDW; 29 January 1925 -25 February 1925 (Box 12, Folder 59 to 60)
  - Warburg, Felix M. to Mabel Coleman; 13 November 1925 (Box 12, Folder 61)
  - Warburg, Felix M. to LDW; 5 February 1926 -13 May 1926 (Box 12, Folder 62 to 68)
  - Warburg, Felix M. to Mabel Coleman; 25 August 1926 (Box 12, Folder 69)
  - Warburg, Felix M. to LDW; 30 November 1926 -22 December 1926 (Box 12, Folder 70 to 71)
  - Warburg, Felix M. to Mabel Coleman; 12 July 1927 (Box 12, Folder 72)